<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ES Dorelan</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 16:38:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>ES Dorelan</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Arsenal Beat Wolves To Go Four Points Clear At Top</title>
		<link>/arsenal-beat-wolves-to-go-four-points-clear-at-top/</link>
					<comments>/arsenal-beat-wolves-to-go-four-points-clear-at-top/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 22:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arsenal Beat Wolves To Go Four Points Clear At Top]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=374</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Arsenal moved four points clear at the top of the Premier League as early goals by Bukayo Saka and Martin Odegaard fired them to a 2-1 victory at home to Wolverhampton Wanderers on Saturday. In freezing temperatures Arsenal made a...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Arsenal moved four points clear at the top of the Premier League as early goals by Bukayo Saka and Martin Odegaard fired them to a 2-1 victory at home to Wolverhampton Wanderers on Saturday. In freezing temperatures Arsenal made a lightning fast start and the points always looked secure from the moment captain Odegaard doubled their advantage in the 13th minute. Saka had given Mikel Arteta&#8217;s side the lead in the sixth minute after some intricate link-up play sent him clear.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Wolves re-grouped and gradually began to make a few inroads although Arsenal were untroubled until Matheus Cunha shot powerfully past home keeper David Raya after 86 minutes to set up an unexpectedly nervy climax. Arsenal have 33 points from 14 games with champions Manchester City, who host Tottenham Hotspur on Sunday, on 29 and Liverpool and Aston Villa, also in action on Sunday, on 28. After running Manchester City so close for so long last season only to fall short there were fears that Arsenal might struggle to reach such heights again this time.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But Arteta&#8217;s side are showing the sort of consistency that is required for a long title race. Just as against Lens in the Champions League in midweek when they scored five times in the first half, Arsenal flew out of the traps to take control against Wolves. The opener was typical of Arsenal&#8217;s attacking play as Saka linked with Gabriel Jesus before Takehiro Tomiyasu played the ball through to the young England forward who smashed his finish past Wolves keeper Jose Sa. Arsenal doubled their lead with another team goal, this time Oleksandr Zinchenko playing a one-two with Jesus who cut a pass back to Odegaard who side-footed a clinical finish. A third goal proved elusive, however, and when Cunha beat Raya with a curling left-footed effort late on Wolves suddenly looked capable of rescuing an unlikely point.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/arsenal-beat-wolves-to-go-four-points-clear-at-top/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xavi Calls On Felix To Let Atletico Criticism Inspire Him</title>
		<link>/xavi-calls-on-felix-to-let-atletico-criticism-inspire-him/</link>
					<comments>/xavi-calls-on-felix-to-let-atletico-criticism-inspire-him/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 22:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Xavi Calls On Felix To Let Atletico Criticism Inspire Him]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=368</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Barcelona coach Xavi Hernandez called on Joao Felix to use criticism from his former Atletico Madrid team-mates to motivate him when the teams meet on Sunday in La Liga. The Portuguese forward, on loan at Barca from Atletico Madrid, failed...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Barcelona coach Xavi Hernandez called on Joao Felix to use criticism from his former Atletico Madrid team-mates to motivate him when the teams meet on Sunday in La Liga. The Portuguese forward, on loan at Barca from Atletico Madrid, failed to convince coach Diego Simeone during four years in the Spanish capital. Atletico playmaker Antoine Griezmann this week said Felix lacked &#8220;consistency&#8221; or &#8220;got tired&#8221; of finding it, while midfielder Saul Niguez also said Felix had plenty to improve on. Simeone said Saturday he did not want to speak about the forward because he was not at the club, despite still being an Atletico player. (The criticism) should be extra motivation against Atletico,&#8221; Xavi told reporters Saturday.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">I see he is motivated and happy, he is being consistent, I am happy with his performance and how he has adapted to the group.&#8221; Barcelona loaned Atletico&#8217;s record 126 million euro ($137 million) signing in the summer and after an impressive start, he began to struggle. Felix scored his first goal in 13 matches against Porto on Tuesday as Barcelona secured qualification to the Champions League last 16. The victory helped quieten the negative noises around the club after a string of bad performances and Xavi hopes they can build on it against Atletico. We have to find our game, the second half against Porto was very good &#8230; we have to be more consistent,&#8221; said the coach.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">We can&#8217;t say we&#8217;re in our best moment of the season, (but) we have had some very good minutes. We have to improve our performances and the consequence will be good results. Xavi confirmed goalkeeper Marc-Andre ter Stegen was still sidelined because of back pain and will not feature at the weekend. Champions Barcelona are fourth after last weekend&#8217;s draw at Rayo Vallecano, while Atletico Madrid are third, level with the Catalans on 31 points. Simeone said his team was still at a disadvantage against the traditional big two &#8212; Barcelona and Real Madrid &#8212; but were always looking to level the playing field. In principle Barcelona and Madrid start with more chance of winning, but in recent times we&#8217;ve cut the gap,&#8221; said the coach. This is about deeds and not words, and we will keep working to keep cutting into it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/xavi-calls-on-felix-to-let-atletico-criticism-inspire-him/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Copenhagen Dig Deep To End Bayern&#8217;s winning Run</title>
		<link>/copenhagen-dig-deep-to-end-bayerns-winning-run/</link>
					<comments>/copenhagen-dig-deep-to-end-bayerns-winning-run/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 22:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Copenhagen Dig Deep To End Bayern's winning Run]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=365</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Copenhagen ground out a 0-0 draw at Bayern Munich in their Champions League Group A match on Wednesday to snap their opponents&#8217; 17-game winning run in group-stage matches and stay in contention to reach the last 16. The Bavarians have...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Copenhagen ground out a 0-0 draw at Bayern Munich in their Champions League Group A match on Wednesday to snap their opponents&#8217; 17-game winning run in group-stage matches and stay in contention to reach the last 16. The Bavarians have secured top spot in the group on 13 points, with the Danish side second on five. It&#8217;s only a few people who know what it takes to come here and get a point,&#8221; said Copenhagen&#8217;s man-of-the-match Rasmus Falk.</p>
<p>&#8220;I&#8217;m so proud because it&#8217;s maybe one of the hardest places in the world to get a point.&#8221; Both teams needed time to settle with Bayern missing several key players through injury. Copenhagen had an early chance when Roony Bardghji&#8217;s 27th-minute shot sailed narrowly wide and Thomas Mueller&#8217;s close-range header for Bayern was saved by keeper Kamil Grabara. The visitors, whose solid backline has been key to their success this season, defended well and came close again two minutes after the restart through Diogo Goncalves&#8217; curled shot.</p>
<p>The Danes can qualify for the knockout stages by beating Galatasaray, who are also on five points after drawing 3-3 with bottom club Manchester United, and they almost snatched a last-gasp winner. Bayern keeper Manuel Neuer came to the rescue, however, with a double save to deny Elyounoussi and extend the German champions&#8217; record unbeaten run to 39 straight group-stage matches in the competition. We just have to accept it the way it was,&#8221; Neuer said. &#8220;They were very well positioned, defended well and were solid when they had possession.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/copenhagen-dig-deep-to-end-bayerns-winning-run/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inter complete stunning comeback against Benfica</title>
		<link>/inter-complete-stunning-comeback-against-benfica/</link>
					<comments>/inter-complete-stunning-comeback-against-benfica/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 22:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inter complete stunning comeback against Benfica]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=362</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Inter Milan scored three second-half goals as they fought back from 3-0 down to rescue a 3-3 draw with Benfica in a pulsating Champions League Group D clash on Wednesday after Joao Mario netted a hat-trick for the hosts. It...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Inter Milan scored three second-half goals as they fought back from 3-0 down to rescue a 3-3 draw with Benfica in a pulsating Champions League Group D clash on Wednesday after Joao Mario netted a hat-trick for the hosts. It was the first time Inter had come back from three goals down in the Champions League and the fight back denied Benfica a first win over the Italians after seven meetings in major European competition. Inter, who had already qualified for the last 16, are level on 11 points with Real Sociedad, while Benfica are bottom of the group with one point, three behind third-placed Salzburg. Inter will host Real Sociedad in their final group match on Dec. 12, a game that Simone Inzaghi&#8217;s side must win to finish top of the group, while Benfica face Salzburg in their final game with a Europa League spot still up for grabs. I&#8217;m really happy with the reaction of the team in the second half. We went close to winning it,&#8221; Inzaghi said to UEFA.com.</p>
<p>In the first half we had a bad approach, we knew the potential of our opponents and we had to take the pitch in a different way. During the interval we talked, we changed something and we played with a completely different spirit in the second half. Benfica broke the deadlock after five minutes when Joao Mario finished first time after Casper Tengstedt headed it down for the former Inter player. He then capitalised on a failed clearance from the Inter defence eight minutes later to double the lead, before completing his hat-trick in the 34th minute when he bundled the ball home from close range from a cross. Joao Mario became only the second player to score a hat-trick against Inter in the Champions League after Gareth Bale achieved the feat with Tottenham Hotspur in 2010.</p>
<p>Inter struggled to get into the game and their first chance arrived when Marko Arnautovic was denied by Benfica goalkeeper Anatoliy Trubin in a one-on-one. Arnautovic, however, did pull one back for Inter six minutes into the second half, while Davide Frattesi scored another goal for the visitors seven minutes later with a well-placed volley. Alexis Sanchez completed the comeback from the penalty spot after 72 minutes after Nicolas Otamendi had tripped Marcus Thuram. Benfica were reduced to 10 men in the final minutes after Antonio Silva was given his marching orders for a late challenge on Nicolo Barella. Inter then went close to securing a victory in stoppage time, but Barella&#8217;s powerful long-range strike hit the woodwork. &#8220;It&#8217;s hard to explain, to find the words after the first half we had then what happened in the second,&#8221; Joao Mario said. &#8220;We made some mistakes, that&#8217;s true, but some details were always against us tonight. It&#8217;s hard to find out why after a first half like that, no one would imagine the game would end like this.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/inter-complete-stunning-comeback-against-benfica/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Haaland scores twice as Man City cruise past Man Utd</title>
		<link>/haaland-scores-twice-as-man-city-cruise-past-man-utd/</link>
					<comments>/haaland-scores-twice-as-man-city-cruise-past-man-utd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 19:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Haaland scores twice as Man City cruise past Man Utd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=236</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Erling Haaland scored twice as Manchester City inflicted more pain on Manchester United with a 3-0 win at Old Trafford to close within two points of Premier League leaders Tottenham. Haaland slotted home from the penalty spot midway through the...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Erling Haaland scored twice as Manchester City inflicted more pain on Manchester United with a 3-0 win at Old Trafford to close within two points of Premier League leaders Tottenham. Haaland slotted home from the penalty spot midway through the first half and headed in a second just after half-time before setting up Phil Foden for City&#8217;s third. City began the match outside the top four after an indifferent start to their title defence. But Pep Guardiola&#8217;s men remain the favourites for an unprecedented fourth consecutive English top-flight title and showed they are a class apart from their local rivals as they moved up to third. A fifth defeat in 10 league games this season leaves United down in eighth, 11 points off the top. United great Bobby Charlton was again remembered before kick-off as legends from both clubs that played with and against the 1966 World Cup winner were welcomed onto the pitch before a minute&#8217;s applause.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But hostilities were restored once the action got underway. After a miserable start to the season, United had won their previous three games but in unconvincing fashion against Brentford, Sheffield United and FC Copenhagen. This was the real test of any renaissance by Erik ten Hag&#8217;s men and they were found wanting despite City taking 45 minutes to hit their stride. Andre Onana&#8217;s penalty save with the last kick of the game to keep United&#8217;s Champions League challenge alive against Copenhagen in midweek could prove to be the turning point in the Cameroonian goalkeeper&#8217;s career at Old Trafford.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But for the former Inter Milan stopper, United would have suffered an even more embarrassing afternoon. Onana had to be at his best once more to bail out some shoddy defending as he parried Foden&#8217;s header and denied Haaland from the follow-up before Harry Maguire hacked clear off the line. However, he could not repeat his heroics from the penalty spot when VAR intervened to award City their first penalty at Old Trafford since 1992. Rodri was clearly hauled back by Rasmus Hojlund, but United will complain that similar incidents often go unpunished for jostling inside the box.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Haaland has attracted some criticism of late for not meeting his usually sky high standards in front of goal. But the Norwegian now has 11 in 10 Premier League games this season and sent Onana the wrong way from the spot. Hojlund had a huge chance to make amends as he pounced on a slack Foden pass to burst clear on goal. But the Dane took a heavy touch as he rounded Ederson and his ball back across goal was fired over by Bruno Fernandes. City boss Pep Guardiola was growing visibly frustrated as his side&#8217;s uncharacteristically poor passing handed United chances to counter-attack and Scott McTominay stung Ederson&#8217;s palms with a big chance to equalise.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">But the visitors would still have led 2-0 by the break but for a remarkable stop from Onana to turn Haaland&#8217;s powerful header over. United did not heed that warning as City did double their lead four minutes into the second half with a carbon copy move. Bernardo Silva was played in down the left and his cross was this time met by a more cushioned header from Haaland beyond Onana. City then took complete control and only another fine save from Onana denied Haaland his second Manchester derby hat-trick when clean through. But City&#8217;s number nine unselfishly squared with his next chance to claim the match ball to tee up Foden for a simple tap-in after Onana parried Rodri&#8217;s initial effort. The third goal was the cue for thousands of United fans to head for the exits, but not before many had showed their displeasure with Ten Hag&#8217;s decision to take off Hojlund. After an impressive first season in charge, the pressure is growing on Ten Hag to turn around a sinking ship.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/haaland-scores-twice-as-man-city-cruise-past-man-utd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
